export const data = [
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Britain\'s high court of law for wizarding matters?',
    answer: 'Wizengamot',
    optionA: 'Ministry of Magic',
    optionB: 'High Court',
    optionC: 'Wizard Justice'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the founder of the Slug Club?',
    answer: 'Horace Slughorn',
    optionA: 'Barty Crouch',
    optionB: 'Kingsley Shacklebolt',
    optionC: 'Cornelius Fudge'
  },
  {
    question: 'What professional Quidditch team did Oliver Wood play on?',
    answer: 'Puddlemere United',
    optionA: 'Gryffindor',
    optionB: 'Chudley Cannons',
    optionC: 'Holyhead Harpies'
  },
  {
    question: 'What wood is Harry Potter\'s wand made out of?',
    answer: 'Holly',
    optionA: 'Willow',
    optionB: 'Yew',
    optionC: 'Walnut'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is a famous member of S.P.E.W.?',
    answer: 'Dobby',
    optionA: 'Ron',
    optionB: 'Kreacher',
    optionC: 'Hagrid'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Argus Filch\'s pet cat?',
    answer: 'Mrs. Norris',
    optionA: 'Bloody Baron',
    optionB: 'Peeves',
    optionC: 'Fang'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Xenophilius Lovegood\'s tabloid?',
    answer: 'The Quibbler',
    optionA: 'The Wizard\'s Voice',
    optionB: 'The Daily Prophet',
    optionC: 'The Guardian'
  },
  {
    question: 'According to the prophecy, who was the other person besides Harry Potter who could possibly vanquish Lord Voldemort?',
    answer: 'Neville Longbottom',
    optionA: 'Severus Snape',
    optionB: 'Draco Malfoy',
    optionC: 'Seamus Finnegan'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the only all-witch team currently in the Quidditch League?',
    answer: 'Holyhead Harpies',
    optionA: 'Appleby Arrows',
    optionB: 'Chudley Cannons',
    optionC: 'Puddlemere United'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the maternal name of Draco Malfoy\'s wife?',
    answer: 'Astoria Greengrass',
    optionA: 'Parvati Patil',
    optionB: 'Pansy Parkinson',
    optionC: 'Millicent Bulstrode'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who revealed to Lily Potter that she was a witch?',
    answer: 'Severus Snape',
    optionA: 'Petunia Evans',
    optionB: 'James Potter',
    optionC: 'Rubeus Hagrid'
  },
  {
    question: 'What do you call wizardkind who can see into the future?',
    answer: 'Seer',
    optionA: 'Clairvoyant',
    optionB: 'Grim',
    optionC: 'Medium'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Albus Dumbledore\'s brother?',
    answer: 'Aberforth',
    optionA: 'Percival',
    optionB: 'Brian',
    optionC: 'Wulfric'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who hosts the Potterwatch pirate radio show?',
    answer: 'Lee Jordan',
    optionA: 'Dean Thomas',
    optionB: 'Kingsley Shacklebolt',
    optionC: 'Remus Lupin'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the magical map of Hogwarts School?',
    answer: 'Marauder\'s Map',
    optionA: 'The Quibbler',
    optionB: 'The Guardian',
    optionC: 'Hogwarts Map'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the wizarding hospital located in London?',
    answer: 'St. Mungo\'s',
    optionA: 'St. Brutus\'s',
    optionB: 'St. Joseph\'s',
    optionC: 'St. Francis\'s'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Harry Potter\'s mother-in-law?',
    answer: 'Molly Weasley',
    optionA: 'Monica Granger',
    optionB: 'Nymphadora Tonks',
    optionC: 'Pandora Lovegood'
  },
  {
    question: 'What part of the United Kingdom is Hogwarts School located in?',
    answer: 'Scotland',
    optionA: 'England',
    optionB: 'Wales',
    optionC: 'Northern Ireland'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the first names of Voldemort\'s parents?',
    answer: 'Tom and Merope',
    optionA: 'Tom and Kendra',
    optionB: 'Horace and Merida',
    optionC: 'Marvolo and Merope'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Harry Potter\'s auntie?',
    answer: 'Petunia Dursley',
    optionA: 'Lily Evans',
    optionB: 'Molly Weasley',
    optionC: 'Penelope Clearwater'
  },
]